const questionsData = {
    1: [
        { question: "3 + 4", answer: 7 },
        { question: "6 - 2", answer: 4 },
        { question: "5 + 9", answer: 14 },
        { question: "10 - 7", answer: 3 },
        { question: "2 + 6", answer: 8 },
        { question: "1 + 1", answer: 2 },
        { question: "7 - 3", answer: 4 },
        { question: "8 + 2", answer: 10 },
        { question: "5 + 5", answer: 10 },
        { question: "9 - 4", answer: 5 },
    ],
    2: [
        { question: "4 * 2", answer: 8 },
        { question: "9 / 3", answer: 3 },
        { question: "6 * 3", answer: 18 },
        { question: "12 / 4", answer: 3 },
        { question: "5 * 5", answer: 25 },
        { question: "8 / 2", answer: 4 },
        { question: "3 * 6", answer: 18 },
        { question: "14 / 2", answer: 7 },
        { question: "7 * 2", answer: 14 },
        { question: "18 / 3", answer: 6 },
    ],
    3: [
        { question: "2 + 3 * 4", answer: 14 },
        { question: "(5 + 3) * 2", answer: 16 },
        { question: "20 - 5 * 2", answer: 10 },
        { question: "(6 + 2) / 2", answer: 4 },
        { question: "9 + 6 / 3", answer: 11 },
        { question: "18 / (3 + 3)", answer: 3 },
        { question: "(10 - 4) * 2", answer: 12 },
        { question: "16 / 4 + 2", answer: 6 },
        { question: "3 * 3 + 1", answer: 10 },
        { question: "12 / 3 * 2", answer: 8 },
    ],
};

export default questionsData;
